MAJESTY A TSOPMO

• San Antonio, Texas • (404) 749 7602 • hello@majestyatenkhu.com • https://majestyatenkhu.com • github.com/MajestyAtenkhu • https://majestyatenkhu.com • https:

A versatile IT virtuoso boasting 6+ years of an exceptional blend of experience, seamlessly pivoting to the exhilarating fields of Data Engineering, AI-powered Chatbot solutions, and generative AI applications, driven by an unwavering passion for innovation and commitment to continuous learning.

CERTIFICATIONS:

- Correlation One & Amazon Data Analytics (with Python & Statistics)
- SQL & Database Course Completion Certification
- Amazon Web Services Cloud Practitioner (AWS® CP)

• Project Management Institute (PMI®) CDC

• Scaled Agile Framework (SAFe® 5.1)

• Professional Scrum Master (PSM® I)

• Professional Ethics Hacking (CEH) and IT System Audit Diploma

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE:

Amazon - Data Analyst (San Antonio, Texas)

March 2023- Present

- Increased Senior Management awareness by 75%, by designing robust and elegant SQL queries to retrieve 2 years old data to identify specific defects and showcased appealing real-time interactions using Quicksights.
- Created a 1-click reporting pull-up Excel file using INDEX(), MATCH(), VBA, and Python for management to get relevant data seamlessly giving me accolades from Senior Management.
- Built a lightweight data pipeline in AWS and used machine learning (AWS SageMaker) to forecast defects leading to an estimated **loss prevention cost of \$ 1 million**.

Correlation One - Data Analyst Apprentice (Remote)

January-May 2023

- Reduced rejected demands due to incorrect prices by 99% by building an Excel Worksheet (using VBA) for a
 convenience store (specialized in confectionery) that simplified and automated the process of calculating the
 total price of each order, thereby keeping up with customer trends.
- Performed **advanced MS Excel functions** such as; (VBA, VLOOKUP, MATCH, INDEX, COUNTIFS, SUMIFS, and AVERAGEIFS) and SQL queries to gather insights leading to an estimated savings of \$ 150k.
- Majesty created Excel Workbook to calculate the Manufacturer's Suggested Retail Price (MSRP), expected revenue, costs, and profits of an indie publishing company resulting in enhanced pricing and cost negotiations of 79%.
- Develop real-time and interactive dashboards in Tableau and establish automatic data collection, refresh, and management to showcase short and sweet reports summarizing car sales data from the first half of 2020 in the United States for a Car dealership regarding its marketing campaign expansion.
- Led a team of 5 in using data analytics and visualization to quantify business inputs, financial costs, and benefits to help management (a wholesale distribution company that imports housewares in bulk and mails

them out to individuals.); make informed decisions on whether the company should implement waste reduction strategies.

Freelance Projects -AI Chatbots, Web Designing, Digital Marketing- (Remote) September 2022- Present

- Majesty is currently finetuning a ChatGPT Plugin using LangChain and GPT-4 API to provide a
 concierge-style Auto search experience for individuals in need of an affordable and reliable car, leading to an
 anticipated increase in engagement of 35%.
- Created a state-of-the-art AI Chatbot for an Edtech Company using LangChain, GPT 4, Pinecone and Zapier to make the onboarding process of students seamless with an estimated savings of 45 hours of monthly labor.
- Built and deployed an e-commerce website for a client hosted on AWS and deployed an automated lightweight pipeline using AWS Devops increasing loading speed by 25%.

INSPIRE WEEK - AgileCoach/Scrum Master, Ottawa Canada/ Douala, Cameroon March -December 2022

- Prevented scope creep and increased lead and cycle time by 205%.
- Enhanced event attendance by 50% by launching laser-focused and creative marketing campaigns.
- Designed IMPULSE (an Incubator by Pan-African Associates Inc) by using the **empathy mapping technique** to dive deeper into the pain of aspiring entrepreneurs, leading to an outstanding post-event engagement of 105%.

ETECHYOU - Founder/President, Yaounde- Cameroon

September 2019-Current

- Majesty founded <u>ETECHYOU</u> which has trained +133 entrepreneurs leading to the creation of 75+ startups with a combined estimated valuation of \$ 2.5 million.
- Pioneered the launch and effective organization of <u>Furious Entrepreneurs</u> ... leading to stunning post-event recognitions from the Cameroonian government, United Nations, and private investors from Canada as the most <u>futuristic non-profit start-up in Central Africa</u>.

RELATED SKILLS:

- AI (ChatBot) Engineering (LangChain, HuggingFace, Dialogflow, TensorFlow, UiPath, GPT 4 API, Eleven Labs, Stable Diffusion)
- **Data Engineering** (ML/ ETL Pipelines, Hadoop, Data Mining, Modelling, Warehousing, Migration, and Automation)
- Data Analyst (Advanced Excel / Tableau / Quicksights/ Looker Studio/ SQL / Python / AWS, Webhooks, Jira)
- Multi-Cloud/ DevOps (AWS, GCP, Azure, Terraform, Kubernetes, Docker, Jenkins, Linux, Vagrant, GitBash, GitHub)
- **Programming** (HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap, PHP)
- **Project Management** (Agile, Scrum, Kanban)
- **Digital Marketing** (Copywriting, Google/Facebook Ads, Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, and Premiere Pro)
- Languages: English (fluent), French (fluent), Spanish (beginner), Hindi (beginner)

EDUCATION:

Bachelor's Degree in Animal Production Technology, University of Bamenda, Cameroon-2016-2020